<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Homlie</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>

    <string name="action_geolocate">Pick Place</string>
    <string name="default_info_title">Default Location</string>
    <string name="default_info_snippet">No places found, because location permission is disabled.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>


    <string name="action_userpolicy">\n
    These Terms and Conditions (these Terms) constitute a legally binding agreement between you and Homlie Services, registered in Kenya governing your use of the Homlie platform. Homlies mobile applications (the Applications), and content, products, related services, information, and communication are collectively known as the Homlie Platform.
The use of all personal data you submit to the Homlie Platform or which we collect about you is governed by our privacy policy (Privacy Policy). A copy of our privacy policy is available here. You acknowledge that by using the Homlie Platform you have reviewed the Homlie Platform Privacy Policy.
Your consent at registration and continued use of the Homlie Platform constitutes your acceptance of and agreement to all of the terms and conditions in these Terms and Conditions, Code of Conduct and the Privacy Policy as well as any future amendments and additions to this Agreement (as hereinafter defined) as we may publish from time to time.
Once you provide your consent at registration, you may change your mind and withdraw consent at any time by contacting us support@homlie.co.ke but that will not affect the lawfulness of any processing carried out before you withdraw your consent.
Homlie may amend the terms related to the Homlie Platform and such amendments will be effective upon Homlie’s posting of such updated Terms and Conditions. Your continued access or use of the Homlie Platform after such posting constitutes your consent to be bound by the Terms and Conditions as amended.
If any future changes to this agreement are unacceptable to you or cause you to no longer be in compliance with this agreement, you must deactivate your account, and immediately stop using, the Homlie platform.
If you do not agree to be bound by this agreement and abide by its terms, you may not use or access the Homlie platform.
By acknowledging the terms and conditions and/or using the Homlie platform, you expressly acknowledge that you have read, understand and agree, without limitation or qualification, to be bound by this agreement and accept all of its terms.
These terms expressly supersede prior agreements or arrangements with you. Homlie may immediately terminate these terms or any services with respect to you, or generally cease offering or deny services or any portion thereof at any time for any reason.

    </string>
    <string name="error_network_timeout">Network Timeout</string>

    <string name="next">NEXT</string>
    <string name="skip">SKIP</string>
    <string name="start">GOT IT</string>

    <string name="slide_1_title">Welcome to Malakane</string>
    <string name="slide_1_desc">Welcome note</string>
    <string name="slide_2_title">Mission</string>
    <string name="slide_2_desc">To provide services through workamanship.</string>

    <string name="slide_3_title">What Malakane does</string>
    <string name="slide_3_desc">Clean business.</string>

    <string name="slide_4_title">How to use</string>
    <string name="slide_4_desc">.</string>
    <string name="app_label"> Search Feature</string>
    <string name="search_hint">Search Fruit</string>
    <string name="search_view">Enter search</string>
    <string name="select_time">Select from time picker</string>
    <string name="not_text"> </string>
    <string name="add_new_location">Add new location</string>
    <string name="location_list">Locations</string>
    <string name="need_location_permission_message">You need to enable location permissions first</string>
    <string name="location_permissions_granted_message">Location Permissions Granted</string>
    <string name="setting_enabled" translatable="false">EnabledSetting</string>
    <string name="settings_label">Settings</string>
    <string name="location_permissions">Location Permissions</string>
    <string name="enable_geofences">Enable Geofences</string>
    <string name="privacy">http://www.google.com/policies/privacy</string>
    <string name="ringer_permissions">Ringer Permissions</string>
    <string name="silent_mode_activated">Silent mode activated</string>
    <string name="touch_to_relaunch">Touch to launch the app.</string>
    <string name="back_to_normal">Back to normal</string>

</resources>
